PHUC

FRONT END DEVELOPER

PORTFOLIO

LINKEDIN

CITULIB

LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Finnish Novice
- · Vietnamese Native

ACHIEVEMENTS

- STHEC2021 hackathon winner
- Full Stack Development DevOps
 Practices certificate by Integrify
- Bachelor's degree in Information Technology.

PROFILE

Hi, I am Phuc Le, a passionate web developer from Finland. I am a listener, a learner, a developer, and a front-end enthusiast. I am open to suggestions, improvements, and opportunities I take great care in the experience, architecture, and code quality of the projects I build, as well as the meaning of those projects.

RECENT PROJECTS

Ngoc's MaxiNutri Web Application

React.js, JavaScript, Redux, Node.js, MongoDB, Express.js, Postman, Jwt-token

A project with the most essential features for modern e-commerce websites such as registration, login, admin accounts, shopping cart, and order checkout. Admin users can add items and update their prices.

STHEC2021 Solution Protocol

React.js, TypeScript, MongoDB, Node.js, Express.js, Redux, Postman, Jwt-token

A full-stack eCommerce website that won the solution to the challenge at the STHEC2021 hackathon hosted by Wärtsilä.

Lofi generator website

React.js, Redux, SASS, Firebase

A web application that can generate lofi music and background sound to help users focus more on what they are doing

Portfolio

React.js, SCSS, Material-UI, TypeScript, Framer

A professional portfolio website developed with modern frameworks.

Job Tracker application

React.js, SCSS, Material-UI, Redux, MongoDB, Node.js, Express.js

A MERN stack application that keeps track of your job application.

Don't bite my hand application

React.js, CSS, TensorflowJS

An application that gives warning wherever you bite your nails when working on the computer.

SKILLS

Front-end Development: Accessibility, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, JavaScript, Material-UI,

React.js, Redux, SCSS, Styled Component, TypeScript. **Back-end Development:** Express.js, Node.js, REST API.

Database Management: Firebase, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Postman.

Testing: Jest, breakpoints.

DevOps: GitHub Actions, Heroku, Netlify, Azure DevOps, GitLab, GitHub.

Align: Scrum.

EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer

- Technologies: HTML, Sass, JS, TS, ReactJS, Node, Git
- Tools
 - Visual Studio Code (code editor)
 - MS Teams (team communication)
 - Figma (design tool)
 - Azure (Scrum)Gitlab (source con
 - Gitlab (source control) Valuable experience:
 - Engaging a full software development process.
 - Follow the SCRUM framework's principles to grow and overcome challenges as a team.

M-Files | Tampere, Finland | February 2022 - Present

Full Stack Developer

 Participant in the Integrify Academy, which included MERN stack's project, Scrum method, and basic about DevOps.

Integrify | Helsinki, Finland | October 2021 - Present

EDUCATION

B.Eng. in Information Technology, majoring in Embedded Systems

Vaasa University of Applied Sciences | Vaasa, Finland | September 2018 - Present

Digitalisation Academy Program

Vaasa University of Applied Sciences | Vaasa, Finland | October 2021 - Present